http://www.rieserfineart.com/privacy-policy/

0
item
items
0
MenuWhat’s NewNew AcquisitionsPoint Lobos, North Shore – Theodore M. Criley CloseShows & Events“THE LUMINOUS LANDSCAPE: NEW PAINTINGS BY KIM LORDIER.”
VIEW AND PURCHASE ONLINE NOW!“THE LUMINOUS LANDSCAPE: NEW PAINTINGS BY KIM LORDIER.”
VIEW AND PURCHASE ONLINE NOW!Privacy Statement Our Privacy Policy describes the types of information we collect from you when you visit or order products from our site, and explains what we do with that … Read More »SEE SHOW INFOThanks To YOU, We’ve Donated $4,165.25 to Local Food Banks!Thanks To YOU, We’ve Donated $4,165.25 to Local Food Banks!Privacy Statement Our Privacy Policy describes the types of information we collect from you when you visit or order products from our site, and explains what we do with that … Read More »SEE SHOW INFOYou Can Now Purchase ONLINE from Rieser Fine Art!
Free Shipping on Online Orders!You Can Now Purchase ONLINE from Rieser Fine Art!
Free Shipping on Online Orders!Privacy Statement Our Privacy Policy describes the types of information we collect from you when you visit or order products from our site, and explains what we do with that … Read More »SEE SHOW INFO CloseFrom the Blog“THE LUMINOUS LANDSCAPE: NEW PAINTINGS BY KIM LORDIER.”
VIEW AND PURCHASE ONLINE NOW!Thanks To YOU, We’ve Donated $4,165.25 to Local Food Banks!You Can Now Purchase ONLINE from Rieser Fine Art!
Free Shipping on Online Orders! Close CloseArtistsFeatured ArtistsBill DavidsonWilliam HookKim LordierCharles Movalli (1945-2016)Michael ObermeyerHistorical Art (deceased)Adam, WilliamBotke, Cornelis J.Braun, MauriceBreuer, Henry JosephBufano, BeniaminoChittenden, Alice BrownClapp, William HenryDonovan, LinfordDzigurski, AlexanderFarnsworth, A. V.Francisco, J. BondGilbert, A.N.A., Arthur HillGile, Selden ConnorGisson, AndreGoerschner, TedHannum, WilliamKetcham, Hank (Henry King)Kobara, Tomi D.Logan, N.A., MauriceMitchell, Alfred R.Morgan, Mary DeNealeMovalli, CharlesMyers, Frank HarmonNicholson, Lillie MayO'Shea, JohnOliver, Myron AngeloRaphael, JosephRedmond, GranvilleRitschel, N.A., William F.Robinson, Charles DormonRockwell, NormanSchuster, DonnaSilva, William PoseySmith, Jack WilkinsonSwan, RussellTeague, N.A., DonaldVan Sloun, FrankWachtel, Marion KavanaughWood, Robert WilliamYuan, S. C.Contemporary Artists (living)Baird, JudyDavidson, BillFritzler, GeraldGibbs, MitchGoode, JaneHaas, EdHanson, CoralyHook, William C.Lamb, JimLordier, KimMcGrew, JamesObermeyer, MichaelPeek, CarolPrzewodek, CamilleWard, Edward NortonZenin, Antonina (Tonya) CloseArtContemporary (Living)Historical (Deceased)Current Dutch Auction Sale – Bid Now!Art AppraisalsSearch CloseAbout UsContactContactArt Evaluation Close
Privacy Statement
Our Privacy Policy describes the types of information we collect from you when you visit or order products from our site, and explains what we do with that information. Our Privacy Policy is effective as of April 2020 and will remain in effect until we replace it.
Information Collection & Use
If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (including, but not limited to, name, telephone number, email, and shipping address) and financial information (including, but not limited to, credit card number, expiration date, etc.).
We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. In order to fulfill your orders we may share personally identifiable information with certain third party providers.
We use an outside shipping company to fulfill orders, and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services.
Log Files
As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click stream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.
We may use a third-party tracking service that uses JavaScript to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate. The information we track is limited to usage and volume statistics and is used to provide insight into the effectiveness of our online marketing initiatives and strategies.
Cookies
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We may link the information we store in cookies to your personal information in order to provide a faster and more pleasant online shopping experience.
We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.
We set a session cookie to store your passwords, so you don’t have to enter it more than once per session.  Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site will be limited.
This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by this site only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers or third-party sites that may be linked to from this site.
Copyright
All images of people, places and/or products posted on this Site are either the property of James J. Rieser Fine Art, or are used herein with express permission granted to James J Rieser Fine Art.  Unless otherwise noted, all content included on this Site, including images, illustrations, designs, icons, photographs, video clips and written and other materials is the property of James J. Rieser Fine Art or its suppliers, partners or affiliates and is protected by United States and international copyright laws. The compilation of this Site is the exclusive property of James J. Rieser Fine Art and is protected by United States and international copyright laws. Any unauthorized use of any content or materials on this Site is strictly prohibited and may violate copyright and trademark laws, and/or the laws of privacy, publicity, and/or communications regulations and statutes. Any use of the materials or content on this Site can only be made with the prior written and express authorization of James J. Rieser Fine Art.  For further information on how you may obtain authorization to use any materials or content on this Site, please contact a staff member of James J. Rieser Fine Art through email at info@RieserFineArt.com.
Customer Service
Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.
Profile
We store information that we collect through cookies, log files and third-party sources to create a “profile” of your preferences. We tie your personally identifiable information, and your purchase history, to information in the profile, in order to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers and to improve the content of the site for you.
Supplementation of Information
In order to provide secure and convenient online ordering, we use a third-party vendor, to verify your credit card information and billing address.
Aggregate Information (Non-Personally Identifiable)
We may share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our agents, including agencies or third-party vendors used to aggregate demographic information, provide marketing analysis and consult on advertising strategies. This information does not identify individual users. We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information.
Personally Identifiable Information
You agree to fully indemnify James J. Rieser Fine Art, its owners, employees, agents, distributors, vendors, and affiliates from and against any and all third party claims, demands, liabilities, costs or expenses, including reasonable attorneys’ fees, resulting from your breach of any of these terms and conditions, including, but not limited to, any allegations, damages or claims relating to any infringement or violation of any third-party rights.
Risk of Loss
Other than as provided in this Privacy Statement, we do not share your personally identifiable information with third parties.
Legal Disclaimer
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we reasonably believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.
Choice and Opt-out
We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, or if you no longer wish to receive our promotional communications, you can indicate your preference on our email communications by simply following the steps to unsubscribe.
Links to Other Sites
This Web site may contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by James J. Rieser Fine Art.  Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.
Be careful of disclosing any of your personally identifiable information when leaving our site. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.
This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site.
Access to Personally Identifiable Information
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by emailing us at info@RieserFineArt.com or by contacting us by telephone (831) 620-0530 or postal mail at James J. Rieser Fine Art, P.O Box 1208, Carmel, CA 93921-1208.
Security
The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can email us at info@RieserFineArt.com.
Site Policies, Modification and Severability
We reserve the right to make changes to this Site, our Privacy Statement, and these Site Terms at any time. Any changes to our Site Terms or Privacy Statement shall become binding on you within 30 days of their being posted on our web site or their being emailed to you. If you do not agree to any new terms, your sole remedy is to stop using the Site. If any of these Site Terms shall be deemed invalid, void, or for any reason unenforceable, that term shall be deemed severable and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining term or condition.
Business Transitions
In the event James J. Rieser Fine Art goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email or prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. You consent to the transfer of your personally identifiable information to any such successor entity unless you notify us via email to the contrary.
Changes in this Privacy Statement
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, which is linked from the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.
All ArtistsSelect ArtistAdam, WilliamBaird, JudyBotke, Cornelis J.Braun, MauriceBreuer, Henry JosephBufano, BeniaminoChittenden, Alice BrownClapp, William HenryDavidson, BillDonovan, LinfordDzigurski, AlexanderFarnsworth, A. V.Francisco, J. BondFritzler, GeraldGibbs, MitchGilbert, A.N.A., Arthur HillGile, Selden ConnorGisson, AndreGoerschner, TedGoode, JaneHaas, EdHannum, WilliamHanson, CoralyHook, William C.Ketcham, Hank (Henry King)Kobara, Tomi D.Lamb, JimLogan, N.A., MauriceLordier, KimMcGrew, JamesMitchell, Alfred R.Morgan, Mary DeNealeMovalli, CharlesMyers, Frank HarmonNicholson, Lillie MayO'Shea, JohnObermeyer, MichaelOliver, Myron AngeloPeek, CarolPrzewodek, CamilleRaphael, JosephRedmond, GranvilleRitschel, N.A., William F.Robinson, Charles DormonRockwell, NormanSchuster, DonnaSilva, William PoseySmith, Jack WilkinsonSwan, RussellTeague, N.A., DonaldVan Sloun, FrankWachtel, Marion KavanaughWard, Edward NortonWood, Robert WilliamYuan, S. C.Zenin, Antonina (Tonya)Recent News“THE LUMINOUS LANDSCAPE: NEW PAINTINGS BY KIM LORDIER.”
VIEW AND PURCHASE ONLINE NOW!June 18, 2020Thanks To YOU, We’ve Donated $4,165.25 to Local Food Banks!May 17, 2020You Can Now Purchase ONLINE from Rieser Fine Art!
Free Shipping on Online Orders!May 1, 2020
Follow us
Site Search
Search
Art Search
Contact
About Us
Shows & Events
Site Map
Shows and Events“THE LUMINOUS LANDSCAPE: NEW PAINTINGS BY KIM LORDIER.”
VIEW AND PURCHASE ONLINE NOW!June 18, 2020Thanks To YOU, We’ve Donated $4,165.25 to Local Food Banks!May 17, 2020You Can Now Purchase ONLINE from Rieser Fine Art!
Free Shipping on Online Orders!May 1, 2020
Dolores between 5th & 6th in Su Vecino Court Carmel, CA
P.O. Box 1208, Carmel , CA 93921
